Hello friends, I am Sagar and a
very warm welcome to all of you. In today's
video, today's budget was seen
and in this budget, this subscription is available,
insurance subscription and here finally
whatever comes in the budget, subscribe subscribe,
for them, let's talk about it, subscribe,
appoint thousands of subscribers, subscribe, let's
talk about the problem, around 550, that is,
around 4% from Triphala point,
okay, so how to
subscribe to this channel here, like,
subscribe, subscribe, subscribe
and try to subscribe, call
snow was appointed around thousand nine hundred fifty rupees, so
now school subscribe was
very subscribed here,
because it is subscribed,
there this company will be
seen doing a good business, so here
we are increasing a limit, then these companies will
also get direct benefit, so subscribe, you
can see here,
this has been talked about in the video for the last several days, subscribe
to the channel, behave like subscribe,
so see here, even now there is a
good investment positive here,
if the boom increases from here, then it will be very
great, subscribe, but then  Also here
you can subscribe to my channel, the
subscriber can also
run very fast in a week, so it may take time for you,
but if this is your
time and place 102 years, then let's
subscribe here, so now school,
if you can
see the subscription from your level in those days,
plus five, this will compare,
in stock last year it made around 1000 here, so if you have
not subscribed yet, then you will be
appointed and subscribed
here, appointment from the top,
but now school, subscribe,
even though Nifty, Bank, Nifty, all these
situations are seen happening, but there is
no recovery of any level in it yet, if you
cross new haikukars, then there are other
ways here, then you can get it, so
all these are the topics which should be
in your portfolio, some
get appointed and some get reduced, this
means that there are a lot of subscribers and
if you had subscribed here, then
you can subscribe here
and
if we talk roughly, then till f-18,
You can see the levels up to 450 here, so
now we have talked about 470 to 40, there can be a
fall of one and a half here,
subscribe to the subscribe button, you must have liked the video, if you liked the
video then you should like it
with your friends, if you have not subscribed to the channel then
click on subscribe.